M: Thank you for calling Saks Fifth Avenue Department Store.
男：感谢致电萨克斯第五大道百货商店。
How can I be of assistance to you today?
有什么我能帮到你的吗？
W: Hello. I was in your store this past weekend and bought a few items.
女：你好。上周末我在你们店里买了几样东西。
Yesterday, my friend told me that the annual anniversary sales had begun.
昨天我朋友告诉我周年庆促销活动已经开始了。
It turned out she bought the same sweater as I did but for a much lower price.
结果，她和我买了件一样的毛衣，但是价格要低得多。
M: Yes. Our anniversary sales started on Monday.
男：是的。我们的店庆促销活动周一就开始了。
We do offer price adjustments within seven days of purchase to ensure our customers’ satisfaction.
我们确实在购物七天内做了些价格调整，确保顾客能满意。
You said you did the purchase here this past weekend?
您说是在上周末购买的？
W: Yes. I was shopping in your store last Sunday afternoon.
女：是的。我是上周日下午在店里买的。
M: That would definitely fall within the price adjustment window.
男：那个时候肯定是处于调价窗口了。
Do you have an account with us?
您有本店的账户吗？
We can credit your account directly with the difference if you wish.
如果您愿意，我们可以直接在您的账户中补偿差价。
Otherwise, we can send a gift card by mail if you prefer.
另外，若您愿意，我们也可以寄一份购物卡。
W: Crediting my account would be wonderful. Thank you.
女：账户里补偿差价更好。谢谢了。
Now that you’ve mentioned there is a sale going on, I do remember a dress I quite liked when I was in the shop on Sunday.
既然你提到了还在促销，我记得周日在店里有一条裙子我很喜欢。
Is it on offer as well?
这条裙子也打折吗？
M: Yes, ma’am. All the new arrivals are 15-20% off.
男：是的，女士。所有新款都打八五折到八折。
In addition to the sale, we are running a promotion for complementary tailoring if needed.
除了打折，我们还有个免费裁剪的促销活动，如果您需要的话。
W: That’s good news.
女：这可太好了。